

ANASTASIIA BUHAIENKO

QA Engineer

Kiev, Urkaine Tel:+380993108863 | anastasiia.buhaienko@gmail.com

Professional Summary

More than 2 years experience in manual and automation testing of Web.

Experience in testing using the following types of testing: black box, usability, functional, Ad-hoc.

Good skills in writing test cases and compiling bug reports (bug-tracking JIRA, Readmine system).

Experience in Confluence system.

The experience of the verification and validation of the technical documentation.

SQL - Knowledge of databases (writing simple queries).

Good knowledge of web technologies (HTML, CSS).

Administration sites on CMS Joomla, Magento.

Experience in using test tools (Firebug, Tamper Data).

Photoshop, Illustrator, Corel – create and edit banners, posters, logos, business cards.

Skills

QA tools BDD (Behaviour Driven Development) Jira/Confluence HTML/CSS SQL

Basic knowledge JavaScript Windows and Linux Excellent communication skills English - Intermediate

Work History

QA Engineer

01/2017 to Current

Infozahyst LLC – Kiev, Ukraine (www.infozahyst.com)

Automation testing using BDD

Manual testing

Functional (in order to verify the feasibility of the functional requirements)

Non-functional testing (testing usability)

Writing and updating test-documentation: test plans, checklists, test cases, bug reports, methodological guidelines

Keeping of tasks in JIRA: testing, writing comments, creating / closing tasks, errors, their description Interaction with the developers, testers, analysts, users of the system Experience in UNIX systems on a user level

QA Engineer/Content Manager www.lb.net.ua – Kiev, Ukraine

10/2015 to Current

Manual testing

Functional (in order to verify the feasibility of the functional requirements)

Non-functional testing (testing usability)

Description of test cases (step by step description of the test case, indicating the expected and the actual result)

Filling content site (CMS Magento)

Design, layout, printing of printing products

Communication with the customer directly

Maintaining social networks (facebook, vk)

Engineer of radio and television Bilink LLC – Kiev, Ukraine

11/2010 to 12/2016

Communication, conclusion of contracts with TV channels

Create and populate TV packages

Building a map network of connections customers

Filling content site (CMS Joomla)

Testing:

Functional (to verify the realizability the functional requirements)

Non-functional testing (UI)

Description of test cases in a bug-trekking Redmine system (step by step description of the test cases, with an indication of the expected and the actual result)

Education

Master of Science: Technology and telecommunications facilities

Kharkov National University of Radioelectronics – Kharkov, Ukraine

2010